Guide to the Records of the Office of the Chancellor/Executive Vice President (Borowitz) RG.6.0.7
New York University Archives
- Series IX: Personnel
  - Women's Studies, May 1973 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Affirmative Action, Advisory Council: Formation, Feb 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224990 7
  - Affirmative Action, Advisory Council: Meeting Minutes & Agendas, Jun 1972-May 1974 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Affirmative Action, Announcement Drafts, Jan 1972-Sep 1974 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Affirmative Action, Association of American Colleges Project on the Status of Women Publications, Apr 1970-Apr 1976 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Affirmative Action, Board of Trustees, Apr 1972-Jun 1972 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Affirmative Action, Census Materials and Tables, Feb 1974-Dec 1975 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative Action, Census Materials and Tables, 1971-Jan 1973 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action Committees, Dec 1970-Jun 1972 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action, Correspondence: Misc, Feb 1972-Apr 1976 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action, Discrimination Charges: Misc, Mar 1975-May 1975 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Affirmative Action, Equal Pay Act, Dec 1970-Mar 1975 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Affirmative Action, Ethnic Surveys, Feb 1973-Jan 1975 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Affirmative Action, Federal Notices, Guidelines, Aug 1971-Aug 1975 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Affirmative Action, Other Universities, Feb 1972-Apr 1974 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Affirmative Action, Personnel Services Division: Numbered Docket (B-31-B-49), Oct 1971-Dec 1971 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Affirmative Action, Personnel Services Division: Numbered Docket(B-13-B-30), Sep 1970-Sep 1971 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Affirmative Action, Personnel Services Division: Numbered Docket (B-1-B-11), Jan 1969-Apr 1970 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Affirmative Action, Press and Journal Coverage, 1970-Feb 1976 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development, Jan 1976-Aug 1976 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development, Sep 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development, Jul 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224991 5
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development, Jun 1975 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development, Sep 1974-May 1975 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development, Apr 1974-Aug 1974 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development, Sep 1973-Mar 1974 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development, Sep 1972-May 1973 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development, Jun 1972-Aug 1972 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development, Apr 1972-May 1972 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development, Jan 1972-Mar 1972 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development, Feb 1969-Dec 1971 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development: Minutes, Reports, Misc, May 1975 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development: Minutes, Reports, Misc, Apr 1972-Feb 1974 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224992 3
  - Affirmative Action, Program Development: School Hiring Policies and Procedure, See Also: School and Division Series 1973-74, Feb 1971-Sep 1973 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Appointments (Including Emeritus), Jun 1974-Feb 1976 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Appointments (Including Emeritus), Feb 1971-May 1974 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Benefits, Mar 1974-Dec 1975 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Benefits, Oct 1972-Dec 1973 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Benefits, Feb 1971-Jun 1972 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Benefits, Correspondence, Misc, Oct 1974-Sep 1976 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Benefits, Death Benefits, Jan 1974-Oct 1976 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Benefits, Faculty/Staff Medical Care Program, Dec 1974 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Benefits, Insurance: Group Life, Mar 1975-Apr 1975 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Benefits, Insurance: Health, Sep 1973-Jun 1976 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Benefits, Insurance: Unemployment Claims, Jun 1971-Apr 1976 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Benefits, Insurance: Workmen's Compensation, Jul 1974 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Benefits, Librarians, Apr 1972-Aug 1974 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Benefits, Medical Center, Jan 1971-Jul 1974 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Benefits, Pension Plan (Staff), Jan 1974-Jan 1976 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Benefits, Sick Leave, Apr 1977 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Benefits, Tax Information, undated (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Benefits, TIAA-CREF, Apr 1975-May 1976 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224993 1
  - Benefits, TIAA-CREF, Aug 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Benefits, TIAA-CREF, May 1972-Jun 1974 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Benefits, University Fringe Benefits Committee, Mar 1974-May 1975 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Complaints, Complaints and Grievances, Mar 1973 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Club, Jan 1973-Nov 1974 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Health Service, Jul 1974-Nov 1974 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Labor Relations, Labor Relations, Faculty Unionization, May 1971-Mar 1976 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Leave of Absence, Faculty and Staff, Apr 1973-Aug 1974 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Personnel Services Division, Office of, Aug 1973-Nov 1975 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Personnel Services Division, Office of, Apr 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Professional and Administrative Personnel, (Code 100), Classification and Compensation Study, Sep 1975-Apr 1976 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Professional and Administrative Personnel, (Code 100), Policy, Jul 1972-Jun 1976 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Professional Research Personnel, (Code 103), Feb 1973, Oct 1975 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Policies and Procedures, Nov 1973-Apr 1976 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Policies and Procedures, May 1971-Jun 1973 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Policies and Procedures, Extra Remunerative Work by Faculty, Jul 1973-Jan 1974 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Promotions, Nov 1973-Nov 1974 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Recommendations, Faculty, Apr 1971-Sep 1974 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224994 9
  - Recruitment, Faculty, Feb 1974-Apr 1975 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Recruitment, Staff, Oct 1972 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Reports and Statistics, Dec 1970-Mar 1974, Jan 1977 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Retirement, Age Reduction, Mar 1971-May 1975 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Retirement, Early Retirement Plan for Faculty, May 1972-Jan 1977 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Retirement, Post Retirement Benefits, May 1972, Jul 1976 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Sabbaticals, Dec 1971-Mar 1976 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Salaries, Dec 1973-Oct 1975 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Salaries, Sep 1971-Dec 1973 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Series X: Public Relations
  The material in this single box is focused primarily on university offices with responsibility for external relations in NYU's neighborhood. The source of much of its content, including commencement protocols, is the Office of Public Occasions, folders 8-13. Additionally, there are limited files on community relations, folder 1, and the Office of Public Relations, folders 14-15, and the University's radio station, WNYU, folder 17. In the latter two areas, financial concerns are again center stage.
  - Severance, Oct 1967, Jun 1974-Oct 1975 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Tenure, Mar 1968-Dec 1975 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Terminations and Resignations, Faculty and Staff, May 1972-Oct 1975 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Tuition Remission, Jun 1972-Sep 1976 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Community Relations, Dec 1970-Jul 1976 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224995 6
  - "NYU Night" Campaign Proposal, Apr 1975-Nov 1975 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers, Radio, TV Coverage, Oct 1973-Jun 1976 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers, Radio, TV Coverage, Jul 1976-Mar 1977 (Box 58, Folder 3.1)
  - Photographic Bureau, Jan 1976-Jun 1976 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Photographic Bureau, May 1974-Jul 1976 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Publications, NYU, Apr 1971-Feb 1973 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Publication, Other, Jan 1971-Mar 1977 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Public Occasions, Commencement, Mar 1975-Apr 1976 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Public Occasions, Commencement, May 1973 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Public Occasions, Commencement, Feb 1972-May 1972 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Public Occasions, Office of, Jul 1975-Apr 1976 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Public Occasions, Office of, Jan 1974-May 1975 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Public Occasions, Bureau of, Nov 1971-Aug 1973 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Series XI: Schools and Departments
  The contents of this series of 6.66 linear feet are concerned with the business of the University's academic units. All schools extant at that time are represented, as well as departments and divisions within them, along with a further set of divisions whose leadership reported essentially to the University's central administration. Those departmental and divisional files pertaining to Arts and Science interests follow that unit's files, while those identified as non-FAS are located following the School of the Arts materials. The impression of an institution driven by ambition, yet neither assured of its place in its "industry," nor economically stable, continues to be apparent in this section of the Borowitz Papers.
  Each component of this series is organized alphabetically. Faculty meeting minutes have been transferred to the appropriate Record Groups. Noteworthy material is mainly found in the school-level and decanal files; material at the departmental and divisional levels tends to be routine. Here too, documents addressing individual personnel matters were removed.
  First in the series, the Arts and Science materials, representing school, departmental and divisional matters, fill four Hollinger boxes and the greater portion of a fifth, Box 59 through Box 63, folder 17. The extent of this documentation reflects this unit's centrality within the University's academic structure, the complex and evolving nature of its structure at the time, and the Chancellor's involvement in its operation. Box 59, folder 2, and folder 7 contain separate narratives of school matters by the outgoing first Faculty of Arts and Science (FAS) Dean, together offering an informed description of the composition of the unit and the range of responsibilities this new deanship entailed as it evolved.
  The role and responsibilities of the Graduate Dean, a previously extant post, remained in flux; Box 61, folder 1 documents some of that history preceding Dr. Borowitz' tenure. Box 59, folders 16-17 and continuing through Box 60, folder 6, holds reports and other materials covering those Graduate School doctoral programs selected for NYSED Doctoral Review. These reviews, a NYSED initiative, were critical to a department's, and school's reputation, involving external reviewers from within and without New York State.
  The impact of the sale of the University Heights campus on its undergraduate arts and science college, University College (UC), was profound. Dispossessed of its real property, UC and its tenured faculty were transferred to Washington Square in a merger with Washington Square College, the undergraduate arts and science unit at the Square. It fell to FAS' faculty and administration to restructure the two faculties and administrations and two distinct curriculums into one, some of which is documented in Box 61, folder 11.
  Business schools concerns are contained in four folders in Box 63 and the totality of Box 64. The School of Business and Public Administration (BPA, the undergraduate college) and the Graduate School of Business Administration (GBA) merged during this period, see Box 64, folder 14. Matters concerning the separate schools and the merged entity occupy Box 63, folders 18-20, and 22, (folder 21 contains a limited amount of material about the Institute of Retail Management, which was related to BPA), and Box 64 in its entirety. Agreement was also reached by the Business School and FAS deans about a new department of economics administratively located within FAS, the availability of undergraduate courses offered by that department to business undergraduate students, and working relationships between FAS and Business School economics faculty, Box 64, folders 4-5.
  Matters pertaining to the School of Continuing Education (SCE) in these years fill one Hollister box. Structural questions, especially program overlaps with other university units and concerns about quality, and budgetary issues (matters of income and expense) were priorities for the university administration and deans of other units. The SCE deans and entrepreneurial faculty worked diligently throughout at developing and presenting a spectrum of offerings, Box 65, folders 1-8.
  However, while "it has already been necessary to make some difficult and unwelcome decisions about University programs," Borowitz, 9/29/72, the local hand on finances seemingly remained a light one, Collins, 2/29/72, folder 8, Smith, 2/23/73, folder 7, Collins, 6/11/76, folder 15, Sawhill, 6/22/76, folder 15. President Sawhill, upon his arrival, quickly undertook "a series of wide-ranging discussions," concerning the future of SCE, 11/3/75, Box 65, folder 17. Following a response by the SCE deans, 11/21/75, a proposed reorganization scheme for SCE, which also gave birth to the University's Gallatin Division, was submitted by Dr. Sawhill to the University Senate, 1/22/76, Box 65, folder 15.
  College of Dentistry matters as reflected in the Borowitz papers fill two Hollister boxes. It was a time of severe strain for the school. An April 11, 1975 Report, Box 67, folder 8, "Problems Confronting New York University College of Dentistry," specifies its major problems (downgrading of accreditation, poor facilities, lack of New York State financial assistance). These concerns underlay consideration by the University in the mid 1970's of operating the school as a contract college for NYSED, Box 76, folder 14, and are well-summarized in Hester, 8/15/74, Box 66, folder 4, and 10/3/74, Box 66, folder 3, and more generally in the two versions (1/75, 3/75) of a NYSED Report titled "Dental Education in New York State, " found in Box 46, folder 5.
  For steps in the process of resolving this crisis, see Hester, 2/11/75, 3/7/75, Box 66, folder 3 and NYSED Recommendation, "Public Support of Non-Public Dental Schools," April 3, 1975, Box 46, folder 5, the contents of Box 67, folder 14, labeled "State Options Regarding Dental Schools," 6/74-7/75, an undated (9/75?) document headed "Reasons for and against Proceeding with the Construction of Dental Center," Box 66, folder 2, "Program Cost Analysis at the New York University Brookdale Dental Center, May 1975, Box 66, folder 8, and the following contents of Box 66, folder 2, Claxton, 4/26/76, Giddon, 7/6/76, and Sawhill, 8/9/76.
  Hollinger boxes 68 and 69, and folders 1-2 of Box 70 hold the records of the School of Education in this collection. Much of this material covers routine matters, for example inter-school course overlap, Box 68, folders 4,5 and unit nomenclature, Box 68, folders 2,9. The School's attention to budget matters is reflected in the highly detailed annual fiscal reports its administration prepared, Box 69, folders 6-8. Future directions of interest to the School can be identified in its "Report on Planning for the New York University School of Education," 5/75, Box 68, folder 5 and its "Mission Statement," 3/29/76, Box 68, folder 3.
  Material regarding the unit initially known as University Without Walls (UWW), a "temporary inter-school degree-granting unit, "Box 70, folder 6, appears in Box 70, folders 3-18. Documentation on some aspects of organizational matters and program start-ups is included, as is Dr. Sawhill's 1/22/76 recommendation to the University Senate that a permanent successor unit, the Gallatin Division, be established in conjunction with a plan for reorganizing the School of Continuing Education, folder 3, previously referenced in Box 65, folder 15.
  The first 11 folders of Box 71 contain papers related to the School of Law and the Law Center Foundation. The School of Law material is limited, and primarily routine, however there is some correspondence indicating school efforts to maintain some authority independent from university administration, see salary levels, Hawley to Borowitz, 4/18/74, and Borowitz to Hawley, 4/23/74, and autonomy of the Law Library, McKay to Hester, 6/7/74 and Hester to McKay, 6/28/74, folder 1. The Law Center Foundation material, folders 6-10, documenting an evolving relationship between the University and the Foundation, is of particular interest.
  School of Medicine material follows, in Box 71, folders 12-17 and Box 72 in its entirety. As with the School of Law, School of Medicine material mainly covers routine matters. Reflective of apparent efforts to maintain autonomy from the University administration, documents referring to probable matters of interest at the Square are more advisory than collaborative. These range from the availability of University Hospital emergency care as a faculty benefit at the Square, Wilmot to Borowitz, 11/8/76, Box 71, folder 15, New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation delays in reimbursing its contracted services with the Medical Center for patient care at Bellevue Hospital, Bennett to Holloman, 7/1/74, Box 71, folder 17 and 9/12/74, Box 71, folder 16, the Medical Center's maintenance of personnel policies differing from those in place for the balance of the University, Bennett to Borowitz, 2/7/74, Box 71, folder 17, and a separate Affirmative Action plan, Box 72, folders 3,4, to the lack of availability to the central administration of information concerning Medical Center personnel and budgetary affairs, Borowitz to Bennett, 1/5/73, Box 72, folder 1. The text of Dr. Bennett's remarks at the Medical Center's farewell dinner for Dr. and Mrs. Hester appears in Box 71, folder 16. Some budget and financial material may be of interest; these documents appear in Box 72, folders 5-12.
  Graduate School of Public Administration (GPA) documents appear in Hollister Box 73, folders 1-7. Renamed the Robert F. Wagner School of Public Service in 1989, a GPA planning document dating from the mid 1960's appears in folder 3. A considerable portion of this modest collection is in the form of memoranda from Dean Dick Netzer to members of central administration, including responses to what he suggests are inappropriate attacks by the administration and/or other units on GPA's budget and curriculum.
  Hollister box 73, folders 8-18 and box 74, folder 1 contains this collection's materials on the School of Social Work (SSW). It was a period of great turmoil for SSW. Minority student demonstrations over reduced scholarship funding attracted congressional attention, Box 73, folder 11. The Task Force on the University's Financial Emergency recommended that SSW be phased out, Box 73, folder 15, press release, n.d. A successful emergency fund-raising campaign, Box 73, folder 15, impelled the reversal of this recommendation. The dean in office when first steps to implement the phase-out recommendation were being taken resigned, and his successor died within the first year of his appointment, Box 74, folder 1.
  The School of the Arts was established in 1965. Folders 2-15 in Hollister Box 74 contain records of its early development. As with the records for the more senior units, much of the material here covers routine administrative and curricular matters. Material found in folders 9-11 is concentrated on the affairs of the school's Alternate Media Center. Of particular interest is its project on Interactive Telecommunications conducted in Reading, Pennsylvania and first funded by the National Science Foundation in 1974.
  As indicated at the beginning of this series, some divisions labeled non-FAS reported essentially to central administration, and limited amounts of documentation for, among others, the Institute of Afro-American Affairs, the Center for International Studies, Sunrise Semester, and Town Hall constitute the final portion of Series 11. All of the non-FAS divisional material is located in Box 74, folders 16-17 and Box 75, folders 1-14.
  - Public Relations, Office of, Sep 1975-Feb 1977 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Public Relations, Office of, May 1972-Jun 1975 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Public Relations, Office of Creative Services; Mailing and Distribution, Dec 1974-Oct 1976 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - WNYU, Jul 1972-Aug 1975 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Arts and Science, Committee of Deans, Oct 1968-Aug 1972 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224996 4
  - Arts and Science (FAS), Mar 1976-Mar 1977 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Arts and Science (FAS), Sep 1975-Feb 1976 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Arts and Science (FAS), Jul 1972-Aug 1975 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Arts and Science (FAS), Budget & Financial Matters, Jul 1975-Mar 1977 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Arts and Science (FAS), Budget & Financial Matters, Feb 1971-Jun 1975 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Arts and Science (FAS), Dean, Oct 1973-Mar 1976 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Arts and Science (FAS), Dean, Jan 1972-Aug 1973 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Arts and Science(FAS), Faculty Meeting Minutes, Oct 1972-Apr 1977 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Arts and Science (FAS), Governance, Elections, May 1972-Apr 1976 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Arts and Science (FAS), Luce Chair, Dec 1973-Mar 1977 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Arts and Science (FAS) Search for Dean, Feb 1976-Feb 1977 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Arts and Science (FAS), Search for Dean, Dec 1972-Mar 1973 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Dean, Mar 1973-Oct 1976 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Dean, Jun 1972-Jan 1973 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Arts and Science(GSAS), Doctoral Program Evaluation: General Correspondence, Sep 1975-Dec 1976 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Doctoral Program Evaluation: General Correspondence, Feb 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Doctoral Program Evaluation: General Correspondence, Aug 1973-Jan 1975 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224997 2
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Doctoral Program Evaluation: Reports and Responses, Jan 1976-Jan 1977 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Doctoral Program Evaluation: Reports and Responses, Sep 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Doctoral Program Evaluation: Reports and Responses, Jan 1975-Aug 1975 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Doctoral Program Evaluation: Reports and Responses, Oct 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Doctoral Program Evaluation: Reports and Responses, Nov 1973-Jun 1974 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Minutes, Oct 1971-May 1973 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Misc, Jan 1976-Dec 1976 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Misc, Apr 1975-Dec 1975 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Misc, Mar 1971-Dec 1974 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Programs, Mar 1976-May 1976 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Arts and Science(GSAS), Programs, Misc, Jul 1974-Nov 1975 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Arts and Science(GSAS), Role of GSAS Dean, Mar 1970-Apr 1971 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    barcode: 3 1142 04224998 0
  - Arts and Science (GSAS), Search for Dean, Dec 1973-Apr 1974 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Arts and Science (UC), Dean, May 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Arts and Science (UC), Misc, Apr 1972-Jun 1973 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Arts and Science(WSC), Alternate Education Program, Jan 1972-Feb 1974 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Arts and Science (WSC), Early Admissions Program, Jun 1974-Dec 1975 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Arts and Science (WSC), Early Admissions Program, 1974-1975 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Arts and Science (WSC), Program, May 1972-May 1974 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Arts and Science (WSC), Misc, Jan 1971-Oct 1973 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Arts and Science (WSC), Misc, 1971-1973 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Arts and Science (WSUC), Oct 1973-Oct 1976 (Box 61, Folder 9)